hollandbulbfarms.com 2008-12-18

# Holland Bulb Farms Privacy Policy

Join our newsletter

Enter Your E-Mail Address

| 

| Privacy Policy  |    
---|---  
  
At HollandBulbFarms.com, we are committed to providing our customers with high quality products. So that our customers can feel as confident and secure about shopping on line as they do with our products generally, we have developed the following policy to explain our dedication to the customer's privacy and to ensure that customers have easy access to information about our data collection and dissemination practices. 

**Customer Information We Collect On Line**

When you visit HollandBulbFarms.com, our web server will automatically recognize your domain name, but will not gain automatic access to any other individually identifying customer information, including your e-mail address. With the exception of this single automatic process, the only information we collect about you is that which you volunteer either when requesting a catalog or at the check-out screen when you are ordering our products. On each of these screens, you have the opportunity to provide us with your personal contact information (i.e., name, address, e-mail). Additionally, when you place an order with us, you may volunteer your credit card billing information and e-mail address, so that we may process your order and timely notify you of its status. 

**How We Protect Customer Information**

When you volunteer personal information on our web site, all such information is encrypted before it is sent to our server. We utilize SSL (Secure Socket Layering) to encrypt your information when transferring it to our server. Additionally, we maintain appropriate safeguards internally to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of your personal information within our company We provide a Safe & Secure shopping experience to guarantee that the information you provide us stays with us, and no one else.   
(Read more about our Security and Safe Shopping Guarantee) 

Do We Employ Cookies? Cookies are small files stored on your computer hard drive. They are generated by web sites such as HollandBulbFarms.com to provide customers with certain features which increase the ease of on line shopping. 

**Our Mailing List:** Removing or Making Corrections to Your Personal Information By contacting us through any of the above-listed means, you may also choose to remove your name from our own customer list, which we use to send customers catalogs, notices of upcoming promotions and other hard-copy and e-mail information. So long as you choose to remain on our mailing list, however, we provide you with the ability to update, correct or change your personal information by contacting us at the telephone number, e-mail and postal addresses listed above.
